Leonardo Simeone

Ballaghduff Kilkerrin Ballinasloe Co Galway

Mobile: 089-9793677

Email: leo-sime@yahoo.com

PROFILE

I am an industrious, well-driven individual who strives to deliver outstanding customer service, improve on targets and always remain open and sharp with regards to commercial awareness, new technologies and innovations. I also have a desire to succeed in whatever role I undertake, using my own initiative and experience as part of a tight-knit team. My experience in Retail Sales and Management, Technical Support and the Technology and Engineering fields, has given me the broad spectrum of skills and a great level of experience, especially in relation to the Technology Field, where my Education and Hands-on experience can be of benefit. I am now ready to bring my experience and guile into a new working environment, and I am very much looking forward to making a real contribution to your business, as well as adding my great range of skills to excel in any role I am given.

SKILLS

- Experience in Telecommunications Tower Work Skill and Installation.
- Core skills in the use of laboratory instruments such as Oscilloscope, AC and DC sources, Compass, Multimeters, Proto-board, resistors, capacitors, integrated inductors, transistors and Anritsu Site master.
- I am diplomatic, even in times of tension or workplace difficulty and aim to strive and deliver a great work ethic, remaining motivated and positive when dealing with customers.
- Proficient in application of Windows, MS Office; Aided Mechanical Drawing; Chair AutoCAD (URBE), Hardware and software troubleshooting throughout different systems.
- Detailed knowledge and expertise in routers, switches, design, configuration, installation and maintenance for LANs (local area networks) and WANs (wide area networks), VoIP, VPN and SQL.
- Extensive experience in troubleshooting regarding data transmission and reception as well as connection problems of any peripheral (printers, scanners, photocopiers, computers, phones, etc.) connected to a network.
- Proficient and knowledgeable in repairing, assembling, maintaining and configuring computers, mobile phones and virtually all electronic devices.

EXPERIENCE

Boston Scientific, Galway Ireland

Title: R&D Technician II

Date: April 2020-Current

Duties Included: Responsible for preparation, execution and monitoring of reliability and durability tests including but not limited to heart valves durability testing, braids fatigue and reliability testing. I am also responsible for inventory in the structural heart laboratory which includes regular stock take and purchasing of material utilizing SAP software as the purchasing tool. By the end of each test I draw and submit a report in the electronic system to be reviewed, assessed, and approved by the Eng. over the test order. Calibration, Qualification and System introduction of new test equipment is also part of my duties.

Valeo Vision, Galway Ireland

Title: Senior Test Technician
Date: June2017-Current

Duties Included: As a Senior Test Technician, I am also in charge of supporting Junior technicians when they were in difficulty overcoming situations which need a deeper technical knowledge. It is part of my responsibilities as well to train newly hired test technicians to the standards required to perform optimally. Creation and Development of process improvement projects is also one of my tasks, projects are always aimed to adhere to the company standards as well as the pursuit of lean manufacturing.

Valeo Vision, Galway Ireland

Title: Test Technician

Date: August 2016-June2017

Duties Included: As a technician my responsibilities include ensuring minimum system downtime across all manufacturing Lines. Follow systematic root cause problem solving and troubleshooting to resolve issues. A broad range of technical tasks carried out which included preventative maintenance, reports generation and communication, daily Setup of Test Systems including, in circuit Testers (ICT), Function Testers, Camera module assembly and test systems, pick and place machines, printing and labeling equipment, conveying systems. Working as part of a team with other technicians and the support of Engineers allowed me to improve and broaden my range of technical skills as well as understanding more in depth the technology and processes involved in production.

Please Note: From November 2016 to August 2017 I worked for VIP Ecig Ireland LTD as a Retail Sales Assistance in the Galway shopping centre.

I.S.I.C.A / Outsourcing Ceragon Venezuela

Title: Field Engineer

Date: February 2013-December 2013

Duties Included: I was tasked with surveying the base transmission stations for Telefonica Movistar for the transmission expansion project, photographic reports and installation proposals. This phase allowed me to grasp the fundamentals of working in the field with other Engineers and detailing accurate reports that were fundamental to the success of the projects. I was also tasked with engaging across other departments in ensuring projects were completed

Leonardo Simeone - Ballaghduff - Kilkerrin - Ballinasloe - Co. Galway Mobile: 089-9793677 - Email: leo sime@yahoo.com successfully. As a result my profile has been diversified and I have had the opportunity to replicate many professional principles in a fresh, challenging role.

Other Notable Employment

- Proyecto RRS / Outsourcing Ericsson Venezuela (June 2012-September 2012)
 Field Engineer in charge of swap out on the RBS 3518 to the RBS 6301
- Hardnet Computer Store Maracaibo Venezuela January 2010-January 2012 **Technical support**
- Inversora S&D Construction Company (February 2008- December 2009)
 Customer Care
- DS Online (video game store), Maracaibo Venezuela February 2007- January 2008 **Store Manager**

Education and Qualifications

- **Universidad Rafael Belloso Chacin.**Degree in Electronic Engineering
- Br. En Ciencias: "Santa Veronica de MIlan" (Maracaibo, Edo. Zulia)
 Leaving Certificate (Equivalent)
- Universidad Rafael Belloso Chacin.
 Cisco, CCNA level 1 Network Fundamentals (2011)
 Fundamentals building wireless networks and Wi-Fi antennas (2006)
- Languages: Fluent English, Native Spanish.

Interests and Hobbies

I have a keen interest in learning about new technologies.